Who's ready for hide and seek?
[cheering]
>> Okay, I'm going to turn around and start
counting. You've all got 20 seconds to
hide, so get to it. 1 2 3 [laughter] 4 5
What are you doing, Astro? Get out of my
spot.
>> But V, I found this area first.
>> I always hide here. Pick someplace else.
What are you sitting so close to me for?
>> Can't the three of us hide here
together?
>> This is mine and Cosmo's spot. It's the
only area surrounded by bushes where
Cosmo and I can do gay stuff for like an
hour before we're caught. 15 16 17 18 19
20. Here I come, [__]
>> Oh, Dandy, I guess you found me.
>> I'll count to 20 again so that you can
have more time to hide. Oh, really?
>> Don't thank me yet, pal. Just get to
hiding. 1 2 3.
>> Get your own hiding spot.
>> Astro, I thought you were going to find
another hiding spot.
>> I did. I'm behind this shovel. See?
I guess I'm not very good at hideand
seek, am I?
>> No.
>> Since I'm done playing, can I go sit
over there? You do you, girl.
>> Okay, you'll find V over by the
treehouse, and Sprout and Cosmo are
doing gay stuff together in the bushes.
>> Hey, don't just give us out like that,
Astro.
>> Sprout and I weren't doing gay stuff.
What are you talking about? Here, how
about you take the picnic basket and go
set everything out while I look for the
others?
>> Yay, I can do that.
What the hell happened to all the food?
Astro, what the hell did you do?
>> He ate all my tuna salad sandwiches
before anyone got to try them.
>> Sprout. He even ate all the triple chunk
chocolate cookies we made. Let me at
this dweeb. Why are you mad at me? Cuz
you're closer to me than Astro is. Don't
be mad at Astro. He was running around
for like 40 seconds trying to find a
hiding spot. He's probably just tired
and hungry. I can't believe you're
defending this,
>> Dandy. You're infantilizing Astro again.
>> Astro is a problem.
>> No, Astro is my best friend. You all
just hate him because he's gay. [__]
this is Dandy's world. We're all gay,
including the players.
>> My violent homophobia has nothing to do
with this, sweetheart.
>> Come on, gang. Let's all make like farts
and blow on out of here.
>> I got to apologize to everybody.
They started the weekend group call
already. Why didn't any tune invite me?
[music]
>> Astro's trying to join the call.
>> Well, invite him in.
>> I don't want to deal with him anymore.
>> You guys are being horrible to him
today.
>> Dandy, he did eat all our food.
>> I'm sorry. Are you trying to talk back
to the mascot of our very game?
>> Whatever. Let's see what Moonboy has to
say.
>> Hi, everybody.
Is my microphone on?
>> We hear you, Astro. What do you want?
>> I just wanted to say I'm sorry about
ruining the hideand-seek game today and
for selfishly eating all the food that
was lovingly prepared by our friends.
>> Okay. Well, is that all, [__] We were
just about to play smash or pass with
all the other tunes that aren't here.
>> Whatever we say in the group chat stays
between us. Isn't that kind of mean?
>> Yes.
Are we smashing or passing Roger's dad
bod?
>> Ew. You're actually smashing Roger.
>> You know how I like the chubby ones.
Astro, you're supposed to choose smash
or pass. Well, Finn made a great point
about Roger being fat.
>> Don't comment, Astro. Otherwise, the
game's going to take forever. Just click
the smash or pass button.
>> Oh. Uh, okay.
>> Okay. I'm seeing mostly smashes. That
means I get seven points. Glisten, your
pick is next.
>> Who is that?
>> That's Flight. Flutter's older brother.
>> Oh, I never talked to him.
>> Yeah, he's kind of whatever.
>> Whose turn is it?
>> I think it's Dandy's. Hold on, let me
pull the picture up.
>> Dandy, was that a picture of my smelly
feet? Astro, I uh I thought you weren't
going to be here. Let me see what else I
have here. Somebody else go while I
look.
>> Sylvester, you said you got a good one,
right?
>> Indeed. I have brought forth a visage so
ravishing that you could say that they
are the champion of Smashability.
>> And we're going to be stopping here for
tonight. Same time tomorrow.
>> Okay, night everybody. I'm going to bed.
Wait, before you all go, I wanted to say
something.
>> You already did enough apologizing,
Astro.
>> No, I wanted to invite everybody to the
mall tomorrow for shopping and food and
games on me.
>> I don't know.
>> We'll see if we can make it baby girl. I
was expecting more to show up. I even
brought all these sensory toys to pass
around to everybody.
>> Well, you did piss a whole lot of tunes
off. [screaming]
[laughter]
Astro, I baked you some cupcakes with
Sprout and Cosmo's help. I wanted to
assure you that nobody hates you for
what happened.
>> Boxton, the most popular tune in town is
bringing Astro cupcakes.
>> Boxton, these are all for me. But you
weren't even at the hideand-seek game.
>> You know how it is. Tunes with big butts
like you, Astro, need to know you're
being cared for, even by tunes who
aren't constantly around your fat butt.
>> Thanks for the cupcakes, Boxton. You can
step away from my property now. Why are
they all burned?
>> Sprout, can I take the cupcakes out now?
Is that what the beeping means? Sprout.
Sprout.
>> Foxton, shut up. Can't you hear? Cosmo
and I are busy. We'll come out when
we're done.
>> I've never made cupcakes before. I don't
know what I'm doing. I'm scared. Sprout.
>> Okay, Boston. We're coming out now. No,
we ain't. We're done. When I say we're
done, Cosmo, what are you
Pizza delivery for my group of hungry
homos.
I forgive you for eating the tuna
sandwiches. Astro, I wanted to join you
guys, but I had work.
>> How are we supposed to eat this when you
didn't even slice it?
>> That's not my problem. You'll have to
throw your complaints to the chef in
back who's making the pizzas.
My sister Scrap says I'm not allowed to
be near sharp objects. If you wanted a
pizza cut into slices, the best advice I
could give is going someplace where the
chef isn't goob.
>> It's fine. We'll just cut it ourselves.
No. No. This is my duty as the alpha
wolf. It's the alpha wolf's sacred
responsibility to provide for his
kitten. Damn thing is too burnt to cut
through. I bet Goob did this on purpose
cause you ruined our hideandsek game
last night, Astro.
>> I don't think Goob was even playing with
us yesterday. Well, I don't remember
whether or not he was either. But if
that is the reason, then his hatred for
you has caused me harm now, too. We're
going back into the kitchen to bully
him. Bully Sprout Goo is mentally
challenged. You've done lost your mind.
Oh my god. Shut up, Dandy. Nobody cares
about what you say because you're fat. I
know, Astro. You're what we call a
problem tune now. So, we're going to
make sure you become everyone's problem.
>> I'm a problem tune. Oh, golly gosh.
Hey, Goob. What are you doing?
>> I'm making pizza. This is my job.
>> Whoa, that device is super cool. Goob,
>> thank you.
>> I use it to talk when I'm overwhelmed.
There's not usually this many back here
in the kitchen at once, so I'm a bit
uncomfortable at the moment.
>> That's fine. If it makes you
comfortable, you can use it. Is it hard
to use with so many buttons?
>> No.
>> I'm used to it. The screen only has six
buttons at any time, but I can swap
between pages if I want to respond with
other things. Do you like making pizza,
Goob?
>> Daddy likes pizza.
>> Hey, we do too, right, boys? Who doesn't
love pizza? Hey, I was thinking about
making a Tik Tok. Do you want to star in
it, Goob?
>> Tik Tok is my favorite.
>> Cool. Here, Dandy. Hit record with my
iPhone 17 that I was able to afford
because despite being a strawberry, I'm
really rich.
Finn. Hey Finn, over here.
>> What is it, Shrimpo? Do you want another
refill for your root beer float?
>> I want you to put on this wig, mini
skirt, and high heels. I just saw on
Waxwell and Gigi's Bad Tune Club's
Instagram that they're going to stop by
here any minute, and I need to make them
think I'm straight so they don't bully
me.
>> Wait, think you're straight? Are you
saying you aren't? I I mean, you know
what I mean? You're putting words in my
mouth. Point is that I need to show
Waxwell and Gigi that I'm the baddest
tune in the bad tunes club. And to do
that, I need the baddest [__] next to
me.
Is this good enough for you, Shrimpo?
Holy [__] I mean, you're not wearing
the wig. I need you to be in disguise.
You're going to make me look gay or
something. Just looking like that. It
was Itchy. I'm not used to wearing
things on my fishbowl head.
>> Holy crackers. Shrimpo wasn't kidding.
He really does got a [__]
>> That [__] sure does look a whole lot
like Shrimpo, though.
>> They're here. Hurry and bury your tongue
in my mouth, you idiot.
>> What?
>> Well, well, well. Looks like the Finn
and Shrimpy Boys finally came out of the
closet. How brave. WHEN GARDEN VIEW IS
ranked number one as the most homophobic
city in the United States of America.
>> Shrimpo, I don't think your plan is
working.
>> What? No. This This is a girl.
Hey, we ain't judging. It's just, you
know, acting on your gay urges isn't
going to earn you any points in the bad
tunes club. It's only going to make you
look like a [__] I'm not gay. Finn is
the one who's into this stuff. I'll be
into it if you want, Shrimpo. Shut up.
Hey, look at this. You queens. Sprout
just went live on Tik Tok.
>> Hey chat, this is my friend Goob. He was
showing me his what's it called again,
[__]
>> This is my AAC unit. It helps tunes who
are autistic like me talk. Why don't we
give them an example? What's your
favorite food, Goob?
>> I like pizza.
>> Hey, I like pizza, too. Dandy, you're
filming Goob, right? Oh, I'm filming the
goods. All right. I said goob. Goob,
right? Yeah, I'm filming him, obviously.
When did you first get your AAC unit on
Christmas 3 years ago? I got it from
Santa.
>> Uh, Sprout, your fat boyfriend, is
eating all the sprinkle cheese. Cosmo
can do what he wants. Stop filming him.
I don't know. I think Goob needs that
for the pizza. Damn Astro couldn't hold
it in. Tell me when you're about to do
that so I can put my face down there in
time. Haha. Hey, Goob. I got to confess
something. You know how I said I like
pizza?
>> Yeah. Well, I don't like the way you
make it.
>> Oh, okay. You want to know something
else funny? I don't actually think that
tablet of yours is cool either. In fact,
we're all getting secondhand
embarrassment just from watching you use
it. Okay, King. Maybe that's enough.
Shut up, Dandy. You're going to keep
filming this, Astro. Come here.
Oh my god.
>> Let him go, Sprout. Tell Goob you don't
like him because he's mentally
challenged.
>> Oh, Sprout. That's a horrible thing to
say.
>> Watch it with the language, Sprout.
We're alive.
>> Ah, Dandy, help me. You're mentally
challenged, Goob. You're mentally
challenged, Goob.
>> Damn, Astro sucks. You're so mean,
Astro. Since when did you become like
this?
>> Haha, this is funny as hell. Wish Sprout
weren't just letting Goob talk back to
him like that. If I was there, I would
give Goob a good kick in the teeth,
right?
>> I don't know. It's not all that funny to
me at all.
>> You always find edgy crap funny, but
whenever it has to do with Goob,
suddenly you're a Puritan. You got a gay
little crush on him or something, candle
boy.
>> I just don't find IT FUNNY. TURN THAT
[__] off, Gigi. We've got places we've
got to be to cause mischief up in this
[__]
>> Well, I'd better get back to work,
Shrimpo.
>> Not in that cute little thing you aren't
[__] You're going to go outside and
wait for me to finish my pizza in my
pickup truck so I can take you on the
ride you deserve.
>> Get out of this kitchen right now. I've
got pizzas to make. Shrimpo just ordered
a four cheese pizza with extra cheese.
And if he doesn't get it soon, he's
going to beat all our asses.
>> Oh, poop. Where the hell is my pizza?
>> Oh my god. Triple, stop.
Shrimbo. Trimbo, please don't do this.
[screaming and groaning]
How do I turn this damn thing off?
[crying]
>> Astro, where are you going?
>> I'm running away, Dandy. So that a
problem tune like me can't cause any
more problems.
>> You're not a problem tune. Just cause
Sprout said so.
[music]
Hey Astro, we saw the Tik Tok you did
where you bullied Goob for being
mentally challenged. And also, when
Dandy zoomed in on your fat ass, we
noticed you weren't wearing any pants or
underwear, which means you just walk
about with your balls out like us. And
we think that's pretty cool. Do you want
to hop on our threeperson bicycle and
come to our bad tune clubhouse? We can
teach you how to really be bad.
>> Astro, don't go with them. Those two are
bad tunes.
>> I'm a bad tune now, too, Dandy. So,
maybe the bad tune club is where I
belong.
>> Hold up, baby girl. There's something
you got to do up in this [__] before
you can go inside the clubhouse.
>> Yeah, you got to tag it.
>> How do I play tag with a house?
>> No, stupid. Tagging is when you write
your name on the door with a marker or
some [__] [__]
>> But I've always been told it's wrong to
write on walls. Astro, you don't got to
do what's right anymore. Bad tunes can
freely do things that are wrong whenever
they want. Besides, nobody's around to
see.
Wow, that was kind of liberating.
Welcome to the Bad Tunes Club.
>> What's Sylvester doing here? Doesn't he
always fight for what's righteous? Our
club doesn't discriminate over what kind
of bad you are. Sylvester gets to be a
part of it because his in-game movement
speed and stamina are so bad that he's
practically unplayable.
>> Oh, I thought it would have been because
Sylvester is on the registry. Oh, we
don't really care about that.
>> Now it's time for your initiation
ceremony into the club.
>> Aren't I already a part of it?
>> You've got to prove yourself first so we
know we're not wasting time by keeping
you around. Bring the [__] boy out,
Waxwell.
>> Get your hands off of me.
>> Shut that hole UNDER YOUR NOSE. AH, LOU,
NO.
>> Your job is to take this push pin and
pop him.
What? I use he them pronouns. Oh, okay.
Sorry. Your job, Astro, is to take this
push pin and pop them. Wait if you use
he them pronouns. Why did you get
offended when I said him? I'm just
feeling they them at the moment. It's
complicated.
>> Okay, I'll respect that. And make sure
to look good while you do it, Astro. We
want every tune on Tik Tok Live to have
a really good show tonight.
>> When's Louis coming back to movie night?
He went to go pee over 5 minutes ago.
>> Oh my god, Yata. Look at where Louis is.
Do you think it's real?
>> Probably. I've seen Louis do way kinkier
things before for pennies on the Tik Tok
live.
>> Go ahead and do it, Astro. It's not like
anybody likes me.
>> Louie, that's just not true. You have so
many tunes who care about you.
>> I don't care about him.
>> GG. Louis said they're feeling their
they them pronouns today.
>> Louie lost his pronouns privileges the
moment he woke up today and chose to be
ugly.
>> Damn it, Dandy. You blew our cover right
away. Sorry, I got a little trigger
happy when I saw a tune's pronouns
weren't being respected.
>> Sylvester, cover the exits. I'm taking
Astro out the back door.
>> Don't worry about me, dork. Just go get
your boy. AH.
>> WHOOPS.
>> DANDY. What happened?
>> Sylvester shot you. I didn't do
anything.
It doesn't have to be this way. Waxwell,
let Astro go.
>> No.
>> Astro doesn't even want to be a part of
your club. You saw how he hesitated
popping Louie. Astro isn't a bad tune.
>> Dandy, are you really being serious?
>> I've been saying it all day, [__]
>> Shut up. From my point of view, Astro is
the worst of the worst.
>> Literally, why? You're talking like this
is personal for you. You didn't really
think we were going to let Astro into
the bad tunes club, right? That I think
he even is a bad tune at all. I just
needed to make him really look like a
bad tune in front of everybody on TikTok
Live. What's that supposed to do? What
did I ever do to you?
>> It wasn't me you hurt. It's because of
what you did to Goob. We all saw how you
treated him in the pizza shop over Tik
Tok live. I knew that if I made you pop
Lou on the very same night, then people
would forget all about how you treated
Goop. They would stop laughing at Goop's
mental disabilities and just see you
going after everyone and hate you for
your evil tendencies. Not Not because I
like Goob or anything.
>> Dandy,
shoot to the left.
Astro
>> Dandy. I said to aim towards the left.
Which way is left again?
Astro. Astro, what have I done? I just
unalived my best friend. Oh, I'm so
sorry. It turns out the worst tune of
all here was me, wasn't it? I failed to
save you. I can't live with myself after
this.
Astro Sprout, what is this place? Where
do you think, Dweeb? We're at the gates
of heaven because we died. GG. Roger.
Sylvester, you're here, too. And
Waxwell.
>> Well, you did shoot all of us, [__]
>> Yeah, you told me Sylvester shot me,
Dandy. But he's saying it was you.
>> Hey, who cares how it happened? We may
be dead, but what matters is that we're
all together, right?
>> I suppose that is a plus.
>> Hey, what's Finn doing here?
>> Life was getting a bit too miserable, so
I self-exited.
>> That sounds like something you'd do. And
Sprout took me with him.
So, should we head inside Dweeb? What
lies beyond the gates of heaven is
waiting for us. But what about all the
other tunes back in Garden View? Won't
they be left wondering where we all
went?
>> They'll join us, Dandy. Someday they
will.
Do us the honors, dork. Take us home.
What are you doing? Hurry up. I'm
trying, but it won't open.
What's it say, y'all? I don't think
we're getting up into heaven. I was just
given a ticket to hell. Dead ass. Yeah,
I think we're going downstairs. Let me
see it. No, I just want to see if my
name is also on it or just yours. No,
there's like 10 of us. It would take too
long to show everybody my ticket. I
mean, our ticket. So, just start
walking.
>> Hi, everybody. What's Goob doing here?
>> I got a phone call from God saying that
he saw you all standing outside the
front gates of heaven.
>> Well, tell him to let us in. God says he
can't do that because you're all gay and
that if I didn't come pick you guys up
and take you back down to Garden View,
he's going to smite you down to hell.
So, Shrimpo lent me his pickup truck.
>> Is that everybody?
>> That's everybody. Shrimpo, you can have
your truck back now.
>> Shut up.
[snorts]
>> Send the rocks [music] across the hoping
follow me home.
Wondering why my mind keeps on spinning.
[music] This is it. [singing] I live to
me. Why? So
[music] why am I like this? Something's
always a miss. Can't put my finger on
it, [music] but it's there. Wait for it
to subside. Put my mouth up [music] by
waiting for the clear.
Is it bad sometimes? I like it when I
[music] lose control. Oh,
there's something in it that's so
[music] beautiful when I lose control.
And [music] I can see the light.
[music]
But I can also see [music] the ghost
again.
I don't [music] know what else
[music]
my not to run away. [music]
Throwing rocks [music] across the state.
Hoping it'll cave and swallow me home.
Wondering how the [music] world keeps on
spinning. Kind of scared of living when
it unfolds.
Hard to see the light when [music]
everything is dark and waiting for the
clear.
[music] Thankful I'm alive but terri.
But hey, [music] I'm still here.
Is it sometimes I like it when [music] I
lose control?
>> [music]
>> There's something in it that's so
beautiful. [singing]
When I lose control
[music] and I can see the light,
but I [music] can also see the bones
again.
[music]
I don't know what else it [music]
is. I'm doing my best not to run away.
[music]